Yastrebov Andrey

me@ayastrebov.com Skype: <u>yastrebov3</u>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ayastrebov

Github: github.com/Ayastrebov

Facebook: facebook.com/AndrewYastrebov

Summary

iOS app developer (including iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch) with five year experience in mobile application design and development. Used to develop both, mobile games and apps with complex business-logic. My goal is to create mobile software with high-performance and easily maintainable codebase on top of clean and useable UI. I am constantly learning new technologies and always try to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry. I've also contributed in some open-source projects, and stay in touch with other interesting community projects.

Technical Skills

Languages: Objective-C; Java; Ruby; Python; Lua

Development Software: Xcode; Eclipse; AppCode IntelliJ IDEA; Netbeans;

Sublime text; PyCharm; RubyMine; Atom; Git; Svn

Technologies: RESTfull web services; JSON; XML; iOS Core Services;

Cocos2D; CoreData; RestKit; AFNetworking; PromiseKit; Corona;

Cocoapods; OAuth; Facebook API; Twitter API; VK API; Odnoklassniki

API

Platforms: OS X; Linux; iOS; Android

Cloud Services: Parse; Heroku; Github; Urban Airship

Work Experience

Agile Fusion Corporation as a iOS Software Engineer since July 2012 to present time (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Shelvz iOS app for redeeming coupons in various US stores
- 2. Jack and Jill iOS game for kids, made with corona SDK
- 3. Fleapop iOS app. Mobile Flea market shopping
- 4. Regivit iOS shopping app, similar to eBay

- 5. <u>ThatInbox</u> iOS mail app, which utilizes mailcore2 library and INK frameworks
- 6. Mobile Appointments iOS app which integrates with build-in calendar app
- 7. Active Learning iOS app for reading, browsing and purchasing epub books
- 8. <u>Chefs Feed</u> iOS app, the first and only chef-powered restaurant guide.
- 9. Athens Educational iPad app for <u>University of Phoenix</u>

FoodMap LLC as a iOS and Android Software Engineer since May 2011 to June 2012 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

1.Menutka — iOS and Android app for spotting nearest cafes and restaurants and provides a full menu with a social integration.

Lanit-Tercom as a iOS Software Engineer since September 2010 to May 2011 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Hunting pro iOS app for patterning a shotgun
- 2. Cafes Network iOS app (branded) for cafes. Allowing people to get new friendships in the particular cafe.
- 3. Recorder app iOS voice recording app with speex codec support

Independent & Contract iOS Development since January 2009 to September 2010 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Various casual games, made with Cocos2D framework
- 2. Multiple iOS utility apps (one of them was top-3 Russian AppStore)
- 3. Freelance projects

Education

Saint-Petersburg State University Mathematics and Mechanics Faculty Specialist degree since 2006 to 2012